var quizQuestions = [{
  id: 0,
  category: 0,
  title: 'No poverty',
  question: '10% of the world’s population is considered to live in extreme poverty. Of these 10% 736 million are children. How much do you have to earn in US dollars per day to be considered living in extreme poverty?  ',
  choices: ['$0.50', '$2.3', '$1.9'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  id: 1,
  category: 1,
  title: 'Zero Hunger',
  question: 'How many people suffer from hunger around the globe? ',
  choices: ['450 000 000', '650 000 000', '850 000 000'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  id: 2,
  category: 2,
  title: 'Good health and well-being',
  question: 'For the first time, research has shown that “sitting down” has harmful health effects that cannot even be compensated by hard training. Those who sit down more than eleven hours a day are more likely to die within three years than those who sit less than four hours. How much greater the risk?',
  choices: ['25%', '40%', '65%'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 3,
  category: 3,
  title: 'Quality education',
  question: 'How many percent of all the world’s children go to school?',
  choices: ['70%', '80%', '90%'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 4,
  category: 4,
  title: 'Gender equality',
  question: 'In 2019, for the first time AllBright foundation selected the industry that is most gender equal in Sweden. The winning industry had over 40% women in their management groups. Which industry won?',
  choices: ['Real estate', 'B', 'C'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  id: 5,
  category: 5,
  title: 'Clean water and sanitation',
  question: 'The UN organization UNESCO has assessed 122 countries’ water quality and selected a winner. The competing countries were rated based on how clean their rivers and groundwater are, how accurately they purify wastewater, and how effectively they enforce laws and regulations to reduce and prevent pollution. Which country was number one on UNESCOs list?',
  choices: ['Greenland', 'Finland', 'New Zeeland'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 6,
  category: 6,
  title: 'Affordable and clean energy',
  question: 'Renewable energy sources are energy sources that do not end in the foreseeable future. One of these sources of energy is the sun which supplies much more energy to the earth than man uses every day. How much more?',
  choices: ['100 times more ', '1000 times more ', '10 000 times more'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 7,
  category: 7,
  title: 'Decent work and economic growth',
  question: 'The Swedish institutet Nyckeltalsinstitutet each year review the working conditions among over 700,000 Swedes in a total of 330 companies. The winners are the companies that prioritize equality, good leadership, small working groups and sustainability. Which company do you think won in 2019?',
  choices: ['Jernhusen', 'Peab', 'ICA'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  id: 8,
  category: 8,
  title: 'Industry, innovation and infrastructure',
  question: 'What proportion of the world’s population is expected to live in urban areas in 2050?',
  choices: ['50%', '70%', '90%'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 9,
  category: 9,
  title: 'Reduced inequalities',
  question: 'Men dominate the highest position when you look at the world’s 100 largest media companies (management and company boards). How many percent do you think are positioned by women?',
  choices: ['20%', '25%', '30%'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  id: 10,
  category: 10,
  title: 'Sustainable cities and communities',
  question: 'Which city was named The Green capital of Europe in 2019, according to the European Commission?',
  choices: ['Dublin', 'Valetta', 'Oslo'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  id: 11,
  category: 11,
  title: 'Responsible consumption and protection',
  question: 'Which brand was ranked as Sweden’s most sustainable in 2019, according to Sustainable Brand Index?',
  choices: ['IKEA', 'SJ', 'Coop'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  id: 12,
  category: 12,
  title: 'Climate action',
  question: 'The poorest 50% of the world’s population stand for 10% of all carbon dioxide emmissions in the world. How many percent of the emmissions does the richest 50% of the population stand for? ',
  choices: ['30%', '50%', '70%'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 13,
  category: 13,
  title: 'Life below water',
  question: 'The Baltic Sea’s only outlet is the Danish channel. Which means pollutions that are let out in the sea remains for a very long time. If one would choose to change all the water in the Baltic Sea to fresh and clean water, how long would it take? ',
  choices: ['20 years', '30 years', '40 years'],
  correctAnswer: 1
},
{
  id: 14,
  category: 14,
  title: 'Life on land',
  question: 'Which of these materials takes the longest for nature to decompose?',
  choices: ['Plastic bags', 'Aluminum cans', 'Glass'],
  correctAnswer: 2
},
{
  id: 15,
  category: 15,
  title: 'Peace, justice and strong institutions',
  question: 'Which country is considered to be the world’s safest country according to Global Peace Index Report 2019?',
  choices: ['Iceland', 'New Zealand', 'Japan'],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  id: 16,
  category: 16,
  title: 'Partnerships for the goals',
  question: 'What is the answer to question 4?',
  choices: ['A', 'B', 'C'],
  correctAnswer: 1
}];
